

Agena Gertrude Kristine

Freelance Graphic Designer

My Contact

- 🖊 agena.gertrude@gmail.com
- 09163326182
- San Pascual, Batangas
- (f) Gertrude Kristine Agena

Hard Skill

- Computer Literate
- Graphic Design
- Branding
- Social Media Marketing

Soft Skill

- Observation
- · Decision making
- Communication
- Multi-tasking

Education Background

- Batangas State University NEU **BS Information Technology** Present
- Alangilan Senior High School (ASHS) Senior High School - Science, Technology, Engineering, Mathematics (STEM) Strand Completed in 2023
- Batangas State University NEU Junior High School Completed in 2021

About Me

Gertrude Kristine Agena, an accomplished graphic designer with 3 years experience, is currently pursuing a BSIT degree. Her striking portfolio showcases expertise in graphic designing showing a strong mastery of Adobe Photoshop and other editing software. Eager to contribute TransferIt's visual identity and communication strategies, they are driven by professional growth and committed to making a significant impact.

Work Experience

Freelance Graphic Designer 2020 - Present

Key responsibilities:

- Creating Visual Design
- Understanding Client Requirements
- Meeting Deadlines
- · Staying Updated on Design Trends and Software
- Managing Client Relationships and Business Operations

Supreme Student Government, Creative Member (ASHS) 2022 - February 2023

Key responsibilities:

- Content Supervision
- **Editing and Proofreading**
- Layout and Design
- **Meeting Deadlines**
- Team Management and Leadership

Integrated School Student Council - Board for Media Spectaculum Member (BatSU - NEU) 2019 - 2021

Key responsibilities:

- Content Supervision
- · Editing and Proofreading
- Layout and Design
- Meeting Deadlines
- Team Management and Leadership

Achievements

Graduated with Honor (Junior High 2021 - 2023

School and Senior High School)

March 26, 2023 Civil Service Examination -Professional Level Passer